export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is Ryujin's full name?",
      option1: "Ryujin Kim",
      option2: "Shin Ryujin",
      option3: "Im Ryujin",
      option4: "Lee Ryujin",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In which year did Ryujin debut with ITZY?",
      option1: "2017",
      option2: "2018",
      option3: "2019",
      option4: "2020",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Ryujin's main position in ITZY?",
      option1: "Vocalist",
      option2: "Rapper",
      option3: "Lead Dancer",
      option4: "Visual",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Where was Ryujin born?",
      option1: "Chuncheon, South Korea",
      option2: "Busan, South Korea",
      option3: "Incheon, South Korea",
      option4: "Jeju, South Korea",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the official ITZY fan magazine that Ryujin likes?",
      option1: "ITZY's Room",
      option2: "ITZY's Diary",
      option3: "ITZY's Journal",
      option4: "ITZY's Fanbook",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Ryujin's favorite hobby besides music?",
      option1: "Dancing",
      option2: "Cooking",
      option3: "Watching Movies",
      option4: "Reading Books",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "On which variety show has Ryujin appeared with ITZY?",
      option1: "Knowing Bros",
      option2: "Running Man",
      option3: "Weekly Idol",
      option4: "Law of the Jungle",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Ryujin's favorite color?",
      option1: "Green",
      option2: "Blue",
      option3: "Black",
      option4: "Red",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which ITZY member is Ryujin known to have a close relationship with?",
      option1: "Lia",
      option2: "Yeji",
      option3: "Chaeryeong",
      option4: "Yuna",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the title of ITZY's debut song, which is also Ryujin's debut song?",
      option1: "Wannabe",
      option2: "Dalla Dalla",
      option3: "Not Shy",
      option4: "LOCO",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Ryujin's birthdate?",
      option1: "April 17",
      option2: "August 21",
      option3: "April 26",
      option4: "September 7",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of ITZY's official fandom?",
      option1: "ITZY Fan Club1",
      option2: "ITZY Army",
      option3: "MIDZY",
      option4: "ITZY Stans",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Ryujin's nickname or fan-given name?",
      option1: "Ryu",
      option2: "Jinny",
      option3: "Ryu-chan",
      option4: "Jini",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which ITZY member was a contestant on “Produce 101” before their debut?",
      option1: "Yeji",
      option2: "Ryujin",
      option3: "Lia",
      option4: "Chaeryeong",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the person you know who can’t stop expressing their admiration for Ryujin from ITZY and considers her a role model?",
      option1: "Me",
      option2: "Your friend",
      option3: "Your classmate",
      option4: "Shela Zanuba Aulia",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is Ryujin's girlfriend?",
      option1: "Yeji",
      option2: "Han So Hee",
      option3: "Park Ju Hyun",
      option4: "Shela Zanuba Aulia",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is Ryujin's boyfriend?",
      option1: "Sandy Saputra",
      option2: "Nam Yoon Soo",
      option3: "Song Kang",
      option4: "Ahn Bo-hyun",
      ans: 1,
    }
  ];